Knowledgeable PCB Designer with solid grasp of development, implementation and optimization of PCB.. Applies core concepts and theories of electrical engineering to design planning and layout optimization. Brings 5 years of experience in PCB design and development.

Work History

2020-02 -Current

PCB Designer

Syntrons Technologies PVT LTD, Ahmedabad, Gujarat

- Worked on PCB design project form schematic to gerber.
- Also worked on Solid works for 3D model
 Assembly, Cam 350 for netlist verification etc.
- Worked on PCB testing ,parts procurement etc
- Quickly learned new skills and applied them to daily tasks, improving efficiency and productivity.
- Oversaw complete life cycle of design, from initial concepts through production support.

2018-07 -2020-01

PCB Designer

Circuit System India LTD, Gandhinagar, Gujarat

- Oversaw complete life cycle of design, from initial concepts through production support.
- Served customers in a friendly, efficient manner following outlined steps of service.
- Proved successful working within tight deadlines and fast-paced atmosphere.

2016-08 -2018-04

Embedded Engineer

Crear Electronics PVT LTD, Gandhinagar, Gujarat

- Research and build hardware prototype ,PCB design,Arduino programming ,testing etc.
- Designed embedded hardware, firmware and interfaces used in smart switch product at crear electronics.

2015-07 -2016-06

Trainee Engineer

Arkay tech and Nanosoft, Gandhinagar, Gujarat

 PCB designing ,Ardino coding and Pic microcontroller programming.

Dipendrasinh Bhati

PCB Designer

Contact

Address

C303, Fortune Sunshine ,Kudasan,Gandhinagar,GJ, 382007

Phone

+919409424741

E-mail

dipendra162@gmail.com

Skills

PCB designing with atium

Very Good

Arduino and Raspberypi

Very Good

Embedded C

Good

Web design (HTML,CSS, Javascript)

Good

Hardware design and prototype

Good

Linux command line

Good

Education

1996- 2007	Schoolling
	Saint Joseph's School - Vijapur
2008 - 2009	High School
	Infocity Juniour Science College - Gandhinagar
2009 - 2013	Electronics And Communications Engineering
	Geetanjali Institute of Technical Studies - Udaipur

Certifications

Microchip certified Pic18F4520 microcontroller at EFY Delhi.

PCB Designing in Electronics for you Delhi

Robotics at EFY Delhi

Diploma in .Net NIIT, Ahmedabad.

Solid works for Assembly and CAM350 netlist verification

Good